{
  "created_at": "2019-12-24T03:08:54 -06:-30",
  "modified_at": "2019-12-24T03:08:54 -06:-30",
  "exercises": [
    {
      "id": "5e01dcae0e9b410552996c8f",
      "exercise_number": 1,
      "title": "Spanish Alphabets",
      "description": "Learn spanish alphabets and their pronunciation",
      "lessons": [
        {
          "id": "5e01dcae8941c2463a7a918d",
          "lesson_number": 1,
          "phrase": "a",
          "phonetics": "a",
          "translation": "a",
          "description": "",
          "examples": [
            {
              "id": "5e01dcae8951c2463a7a914d",
              "sentence": "Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet",
              "translation": "consectetur adipiscing elit"
            },
            {
              "id": "5e01dcae8952c2463a7a014d",
              "sentence": "Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet",
              "translation": "consectetur adipiscing elit"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "id": "5e01dcae5f3c81f55339ac4e",
          "lesson_number": 2,
          "phrase": "b",
          "phonetics": "be",
          "translation": "b",
          "description": "",
          "examples": []
        },
        {
          "id": "5e01dcaef0059315b22287b6",
          "lesson_number": 3,
          "phrase": "c",
          "phonetics": "ce",
          "translation": "c",
          "description": "",
          "examples": []
        },
        {
          "id": "5e01dcae56604578385c8f54",
          "lesson_number": 4,
          "phrase": "d",
          "phonetics": "de",
          "translation": "d",
          "description": "",
          "examples": []
        },
        {
          "id": "5e01dcaea58adb6864408777",
          "lesson_number": 5,
          "phrase": "e",
          "phonetics": "e",
          "translation": "e",
          "description": "",
          "examples": []
        }
      ],
      "quiz": [
        {
          "id": "5e01dcaeaf60ee949362503c",
          "question_number": 1,
          "question": "Select correct pronunciation for <b>a</b>",
          "type": "mcq",
          "hint": "",
          "correct_answer": "a",
          "options": [
            "ae",
            "aha",
            "a",
            "aa"
          ]
        },
        {
          "id": "5e01dcae87b20232f432ecde",
          "question_number": 2,
          "question": "Type correct pronunciation for <b>b</b>",
          "type": "type",
          "hint": "",
          "correct_answer": "be",
          "options": []
        },
        {
          "id": "5e01dcae0803b2c03f3cee25",
          "question_number": 3,
          "question": "Select correct pronunciation for <b>c</b>",
          "type": "mcq",
          "hint": "",
          "correct_answer": "ce",
          "options": [
            "cae",
            "ca",
            "c",
            "ce"
          ]
        },
        {
          "id": "5e01dcaed67b7f27776bad38",
          "question_number": 4,
          "question": "Select correct pronunciation for <b>d</b>",
          "type": "mcq",
          "hint": "",
          "correct_answer": "de",
          "options": [
            "de",
            "d",
            "da",
            "di"
          ]
        },
        {
          "id": "5e01dcaed68baa6ef48add80",
          "question_number": 5,
          "question": "Select correct pronunciation for <b>e</b>",
          "type": "mcq",
          "hint": "",
          "correct_answer": "e",
          "options": [
            "i",
            "ee",
            "ih",
            "e"
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "6e01dcae0e9b410552996c8f",
      "exercise_number": 2,
      "title": "Spanish Numbers",
      "description": "Learn spanish numbers",
      "lessons": [
        {
          "id": "6e01dcae8941c2463a7a918d",
          "lesson_number": 1,
          "phrase": "uno",
          "phonetics": "uno",
          "translation": "one",
          "description": "",
          "examples": []
        },
        {
          "id": "6e01dcae5f3c81f55339ac4e",
          "lesson_number": 2,
          "phrase": "dos",
          "phonetics": "dos",
          "translation": "two",
          "description": "",
          "examples": []
        },
        {
          "id": "6e01dcaef0059315b22287b6",
          "lesson_number": 3,
          "phrase": "tres",
          "phonetics": "tres",
          "translation": "three",
          "description": "",
          "examples": []
        },
        {
          "id": "6e01dcae56604578385c8f54",
          "lesson_number": 4,
          "phrase": "cuatro",
          "phonetics": "cuatro",
          "translation": "four",
          "description": "",
          "examples": []
        },
        {
          "id": "6e01dcaea58adb6864408777",
          "lesson_number": 5,
          "phrase": "cinco",
          "phonetics": "cinco",
          "translation": "five",
          "description": "",
          "examples": []
        }
      ],
      "quiz": [
        {
          "id": "6e01dcaeaf60ee949362503c",
          "question_number": 1,
          "question": "What does <b>uno</b> means",
          "type": "mcq",
          "hint": "",
          "correct_answer": "one",
          "options": [
            "two",
            "one",
            "three",
            "ten"
          ]
        },
        {
          "id": "6e01dcae87b20232f432ecde",
          "question_number": 2,
          "question": "What does <b>dos</b> means",
          "type": "type",
          "hint": "",
          "correct_answer": "two",
          "options": []
        },
        {
          "id": "6e01dcae0803b2c03f3cee25",
          "question_number": 3,
          "question": "What does <b>tres</b> means",
          "type": "mcq",
          "hint": "",
          "correct_answer": "three",
          "options": [
            "five",
            "two",
            "one",
            "three"
          ]
        },
        {
          "id": "6e01dcaed67b7f27776bad38",
          "question_number": 4,
          "question": "What does <b>cuatro</b> means",
          "type": "mcq",
          "hint": "",
          "correct_answer": "four",
          "options": [
            "four",
            "one",
            "two",
            "three"
          ]
        },
        {
          "id": "6e01dcaed68baa6ef48add80",
          "question_number": 5,
          "question": "What does <b>cinco</b> means",
          "type": "mcq",
          "hint": "",
          "correct_answer": "five",
          "options": [
            "one",
            "five",
            "two",
            "three"
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "7e01dcae0e9b410552996c8f",
      "exercise_number": 3,
      "title": "Spanish Alphabets part 2",
      "description": "Learn spanish alphabets and their pronunciation",
      "lessons": [
        {
          "id": "7e01dcae8941c2463a7a918d",
          "lesson_number": 1,
          "phrase": "a",
          "phonetics": "a",
          "translation": "a",
          "description": "",
          "examples": []
        },
        {
          "id": "7e01dcae5f3c81f55339ac4e",
          "lesson_number": 2,
          "phrase": "b",
          "phonetics": "be",
          "translation": "b",
          "description": "",
          "examples": []
        },
        {
          "id": "7e01dcaef0059315b22287b6",
          "lesson_number": 3,
          "phrase": "c",
          "phonetics": "ce",
          "translation": "c",
          "description": "",
          "examples": []
        },
        {
          "id": "7e01dcae56604578385c8f54",
          "lesson_number": 4,
          "phrase": "d",
          "phonetics": "de",
          "translation": "d",
          "description": "",
          "examples": []
        },
        {
          "id": "7e01dcaea58adb6864408777",
          "lesson_number": 5,
          "phrase": "e",
          "phonetics": "e",
          "translation": "e",
          "description": "",
          "examples": []
        }
      ],
      "quiz": [
        {
          "id": "7e01dcaeaf60ee949362503c",
          "question_number": 1,
          "question": "Select correct pronunciation for <b>a</b>",
          "type": "mcq",
          "hint": "",
          "correct_answer": "a",
          "options": [
            "ae",
            "aha",
            "a",
            "aa"
          ]
        },
        {
          "id": "7e01dcae87b20232f432ecde",
          "question_number": 2,
          "question": "Type correct pronunciation for <b>b</b>",
          "type": "type",
          "hint": "",
          "correct_answer": "be",
          "options": []
        },
        {
          "id": "7e01dcae0803b2c03f3cee25",
          "question_number": 3,
          "question": "Select correct pronunciation for <b>c</b>",
          "type": "mcq",
          "hint": "",
          "correct_answer": "ce",
          "options": [
            "cae",
            "ca",
            "c",
            "ce"
          ]
        },
        {
          "id": "7e01dcaed67b7f27776bad38",
          "question_number": 4,
          "question": "Select correct pronunciation for <b>d</b>",
          "type": "mcq",
          "hint": "",
          "correct_answer": "de",
          "options": [
            "de",
            "d",
            "da",
            "di"
          ]
        },
        {
          "id": "7e01dcaed68baa6ef48add80",
          "question_number": 5,
          "question": "Select correct pronunciation for <b>e</b>",
          "type": "mcq",
          "hint": "",
          "correct_answer": "e",
          "options": [
            "i",
            "ee",
            "ih",
            "e"
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "8e01dcae0e9b410552996c8f",
      "exercise_number": 4,
      "title": "Spanish Alphabets part 3",
      "description": "Learn spanish alphabets and their pronunciation",
      "lessons": [
        {
          "id": "8e01dcae8941c2463a7a918d",
          "lesson_number": 1,
          "phrase": "a",
          "phonetics": "a",
          "translation": "a",
          "description": "",
          "examples": []
        },
        {
          "id": "8e01dcae5f3c81f55339ac4e",
          "lesson_number": 2,
          "phrase": "b",
          "phonetics": "be",
          "translation": "b",
          "description": "",
          "examples": []
        },
        {
          "id": "8e01dcaef0059315b22287b6",
          "lesson_number": 3,
          "phrase": "c",
          "phonetics": "ce",
          "translation": "c",
          "description": "",
          "examples": []
        },
        {
          "id": "8e01dcae56604578385c8f54",
          "lesson_number": 4,
          "phrase": "d",
          "phonetics": "de",
          "translation": "d",
          "description": "",
          "examples": []
        },
        {
          "id": "8e01dcaea58adb6864408777",
          "lesson_number": 5,
          "phrase": "e",
          "phonetics": "e",
          "translation": "e",
          "description": "",
          "examples": []
        }
      ],
      "quiz": [
        {
          "id": "8e01dcaeaf60ee949362503c",
          "question_number": 1,
          "question": "Select correct pronunciation for <b>a</b>",
          "type": "mcq",
          "hint": "",
          "correct_answer": "a",
          "options": [
            "ae",
            "aha",
            "a",
            "aa"
          ]
        },
        {
          "id": "8e01dcae87b20232f432ecde",
          "question_number": 2,
          "question": "Type correct pronunciation for <b>b</b>",
          "type": "type",
          "hint": "",
          "correct_answer": "be",
          "options": []
        },
        {
          "id": "8e01dcae0803b2c03f3cee25",
          "question_number": 3,
          "question": "Select correct pronunciation for <b>c</b>",
          "type": "mcq",
          "hint": "",
          "correct_answer": "ce",
          "options": [
            "cae",
            "ca",
            "c",
            "ce"
          ]
        },
        {
          "id": "8e01dcaed67b7f27776bad38",
          "question_number": 4,
          "question": "Select correct pronunciation for <b>d</b>",
          "type": "mcq",
          "hint": "",
          "correct_answer": "de",
          "options": [
            "de",
            "d",
            "da",
            "di"
          ]
        },
        {
          "id": "8e01dcaed68baa6ef48add80",
          "question_number": 5,
          "question": "Select correct pronunciation for <b>e</b>",
          "type": "mcq",
          "hint": "",
          "correct_answer": "e",
          "options": [
            "i",
            "ee",
            "ih",
            "e"
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "9e01dcae0e9b410552996c8f",
      "exercise_number": 5,
      "title": "Spanish Alphabets part 4",
      "description": "Learn spanish alphabets and their pronunciation",
      "lessons": [
        {
          "id": "9e01dcae8941c2463a7a918d",
          "lesson_number": 1,
          "phrase": "a",
          "phonetics": "a",
          "translation": "a",
          "description": "",
          "examples": []
        },
        {
          "id": "9e01dcae5f3c81f55339ac4e",
          "lesson_number": 2,
          "phrase": "b",
          "phonetics": "be",
          "translation": "b",
          "description": "",
          "examples": []
        },
        {
          "id": "9e01dcaef0059315b22287b6",
          "lesson_number": 3,
          "phrase": "c",
          "phonetics": "ce",
          "translation": "c",
          "description": "",
          "examples": []
        },
        {
          "id": "9e01dcae56604578385c8f54",
          "lesson_number": 4,
          "phrase": "d",
          "phonetics": "de",
          "translation": "d",
          "description": "",
          "examples": []
        },
        {
          "id": "9e01dcaea58adb6864408777",
          "lesson_number": 5,
          "phrase": "e",
          "phonetics": "e",
          "translation": "e",
          "description": "",
          "examples": []
        }
      ],
      "quiz": [
        {
          "id": "9e01dcaeaf60ee949362503c",
          "question_number": 1,
          "question": "Select correct pronunciation for <b>a</b>",
          "type": "mcq",
          "hint": "",
          "correct_answer": "a",
          "options": [
            "ae",
            "aha",
            "a",
            "aa"
          ]
        },
        {
          "id": "9e01dcae87b20232f432ecde",
          "question_number": 2,
          "question": "Type correct pronunciation for <b>b</b>",
          "type": "type",
          "hint": "",
          "correct_answer": "be",
          "options": []
        },
        {
          "id": "9e01dcae0803b2c03f3cee25",
          "question_number": 3,
          "question": "Select correct pronunciation for <b>c</b>",
          "type": "mcq",
          "hint": "",
          "correct_answer": "ce",
          "options": [
            "cae",
            "ca",
            "c",
            "ce"
          ]
        },
        {
          "id": "9e01dcaed67b7f27776bad38",
          "question_number": 4,
          "question": "Select correct pronunciation for <b>d</b>",
          "type": "mcq",
          "hint": "",
          "correct_answer": "de",
          "options": [
            "de",
            "d",
            "da",
            "di"
          ]
        },
        {
          "id": "9e01dcaed68baa6ef48add80",
          "question_number": 5,
          "question": "Select correct pronunciation for <b>e</b>",
          "type": "mcq",
          "hint": "",
          "correct_answer": "e",
          "options": [
            "i",
            "ee",
            "ih",
            "e"
          ]
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}